I think that all of the greatest traders
have to go through some sort of struggle
because that struggle will teach you
risk management. That struggle will
teach you how to be humble. That
struggle will teach you how to grade
your setups. Without struggle, without
failure, you will not know what you're
capable of and you will not know what
works. For me, I realized that I was a
deer in headlights. So, anytime a stock
would go against me or anytime I would
get into trouble, man, I just couldn't
click the button. I just couldn't click
it. You know [clears throat] what I'm
saying? So, I had to have the broker
come in and do it for me. What does that
mean? I had to set a max loss auto
liquidation. So, if my account got to
minus $5,000, I wouldn't even have to
click the mouse. I would get auto
liquidated out.
>> Okay?
>> You know, if I would add to my losers
consistently, I would set a max size on
my account. So, let's say it's 10,000
shares. I could not keep adding to a
loser and add to a loser over 10,000
shares and balloon my risk. So, I think
it's mandatory as a retail trader to
have some sort of loss limits in place
because that's like jumping out of a
plane and not having a parachute. That's
like driving a Ferrari and not having a
seat belt, you know? It's like hopping
in the water with sharks and not having
a shark cage, right? I mean, you could
do it. You're probably going to [__]
die. I say screw your average, man.
Screw your average. Why? If the stock is
going in your favor, I don't care what
my average is because the more the stock
goes in my favor, the higher my win rate
gets on the stock. Your house is on
fire. Do you think the best way to get
your house out of fire is to add more
gas? Or do you think you should add
water? When a house is on fire, that
means your trading is wrong. That means
you're wrong on a trade. These idiots
are adding gasoline to their fire.
They're making their fire larger and
larger, and they're like, "Why the hell
is my house burning down faster?
Markets, [music] speculation, and risk.
This is the Chat with Traders podcast.
Traders, welcome back to another episode
of Chat with Traders. I'm your host,
Kevin Avery. Now, from time to time, we
bring guests back on the show, not to
revisit the same conversation, but to
understand how they've evolved. In
trading, longevity is defined by
adaptation. And those who remain
consistent over time are often those who
have refined not just their strategy but
their way of thinking. Now today's
guest, he's no stranger. Someone who
first appeared on Chat with Traders in
episode 104. At the time, he was very
aggressive, a developing trader in your
early 20s, navigating the realities of
risk execution and the challenges that
come with finding consistency. Since
then, his career has progressed
significantly. Alex Tameiz is now a
professional trader and co-founder of my
investing club. Recognized for his
specialization in short selling low-flat
small cap momentum stocks. His focus has
been on identifying moments of momentum
exhaustion within highly volatile
environments and executing with
precision. He has also become known for
his emphasis on transparency, including
trading in real time and maintaining a
structured process-driven approach to
the market. What makes his story
particularly compelling is the
trajectory. He went from working as a
Starbucks barista, funding a small
personal trading account, to building
over $16 million in verified trading
profits over the course of his career.
What makes this conversation
particularly relevant is the contrast
between where he started and where he is
today. In his earlier appearance, Alex
spoke openly about the challenges he
faced early in his career, including
account drawdowns, difficulty managing
risk, and operating with a highly
aggressive approach to trading. Those
experiences played a significant role in
shaping the framework he operates within
today. Prior to trading, his path was
far from conventional. He funded his
trading account by selling the rims from
his car. We're going to find out if he
bought those back. And then he started
with just the $2,000 there. The early
struggles on the long side of the market
ultimately led him to focus now on the
short selling where he began to really
develop his edge. So in this
conversation, we're going to focus on
evolution. We discuss what's changed
from his earlier years to now, how his
approach to risk has adapted in a market
environment characterized by
increasingly extended moves in small cap
stocks and how he currently approaches
one of his core setups, the first red
day. This discussion centers on process,
discipline, and the ongoing adjustments
required to remain effective in a
constantly changing market. Now, with
that, here is my conversation with Alex
to Miz. Alex, welcome back to Chat with
Traders.
>> It's good to be back, man. It's crazy
because this is the 10year anniversary,
I'm pretty sure. Right.
>> Yeah, it's been 10 years. So, I want to
talk about that evolution. I mean, what
was the Alex of 10 years ago? How's Alex
evolved in that time?
>> Man, I can't even believe that guy. And
that guy was a kid. He was a real kid.
And you know, I still consider myself a
kid at heart. But just to kind of go
back and, you know, I was actually
listening to that podcast again. And my
voice sounded different. I would talk a
little bit slower. Um maybe I was using
some uh vulgar language from time to
time, but it's just amazing how much my
trading, my life, and everything around
me has changed. You know, back then I
was a single guy. Now I'm married. You
know, back then I was living in New
Jersey with my parents. Now I'm in Miami
living with my wife. You know, back
then, you know, my biggest day was
probably actually that was recorded
right before my biggest day actually. So
that was recorded right before my first
$100,000 day. And now, you know, my
biggest day is like eight, nine times
that, you know. So, it's just crazy how
much things have changed. It's good to
be back on the show. I appreciate you
guys having me back here.
>> Yeah. Let's hope the next biggest day is
going to be a little bit thereafter from
this episode. Uh but thank you so much
for coming on. So what do you what
stands out the most from now until then?
What's changed you think the most in
your trading?
>> So great question. I think what's
changed is not only my understanding and
respect of risk,
>> but my uh my my transition into more
aggressive trading on specific
scenarios. Back then, I was like a
gunslinger. I I understood risk, but I
didn't appreciate it and I didn't fear
it. Uh, back then I was being aggressive
on any single setup that was available.
Now I'm very particular. I'm very
selective with how I scale in and how I
size up. So that transition from
immature
gunslinging child into mature
professional trader, I mean I think
would be one of the biggest things
that's changed. H yeah, let's go back to
the origin story. I mean, a lot of the
traders have heard it. So, let's just uh
preface with that a little bit. When you
were working as the barista, this is
what 12 years ago now at this point. And
uh you sold the rims off your car to
fund that first account. Couple thousand
>> confirmed.
>> And your girlfriend had left you at the
time. You and I heard you say that that
was your last try. That 2,000 was your
last try. I'm curious looking back if
VGGL, the ticker you traded that worked
out the first short, if that had gone
the other way, what do you think would
have happened?
>> I'm a big uh Avengers movie guy.
>> Yeah, the biggest things in the Avengers
is the multiverse. So, there might have
been a multiverse where Alex was just
back at Starbucks. You know, I always
thought that when I was, you know, at
Starbucks that I would eventually go off
to own like five or 10 or 15 different
Starbuckses because I've heard from a
friend that some guy owned like 15
Dunkin Donutses and he became a
millionaire.
>> So, I was like, you know, worst case
scenario, you know, maybe I'll just kind
of go on this Starbucks path forever.
And, you know, maybe in that alternate
universe, if VGGL didn't kind of go down
that day, that's where I would have
been. Who knows? Would it have I have
turned out to be a regional manager?
when I had turned out to be a
>> who know maybe my life would have been
better less stress but [laughter]
>> you were destined for greatness. I mean
I that's what I was thinking when I
heard that because you had a $2,000
count. You made a thousand on that short
that that was a heavy position at that
time and like you said you you did not
maybe you didn't respect the risk at
that time or you didn't have a fear for
it back then
>> but it favored you in that moment.
>> Yeah. It's crazy. It's crazy because,
you know, I started off trading on the
long side because I was taught buy the
breakout. You know, buy the breakout is
the beginner strategy that's easy to
understand. Stock breaks out, you buy it
and it goes higher. But what you have to
understand about buying the breakout is
buying the breakout only works in a
certain market environment. Right now,
as we're recording this, it's March
31st. you know, stock market is down,
you know, 10% on the year. Oil is up,
you know, massive to $105 a barrel. And
right now, you try buying the breakout
on anything that's not oil, you're dead,
you know, but had you tried to buy the
breakout four months ago, you'd be the
best trader in the world. So what I
didn't know back then is I didn't know
that, you know, there's certain things
that only work based on the appropriate
market cycle, you know.
>> So that's kind of what I think is super
important. And then what I ended up
doing is every time I would buy a
breakout, it would just crash down. I
was like, dude, how the hell am I ever
going to make money doing this?
>> And eventually I discovered something
called short selling, which is making
money when the stock goes down. So, you
know, when you're open up your brokerage
platform, there's a buy button and
there's a short button. I was like,
dude, instead of hitting buy, if I hit
short, you know, I'm going to get rich.
And that's kind of where that first
trade happened on VGGL. I shorted 2,000
shares at $4 a share, made $1,000, and
from there, I was hooked. That's that's
what changed everything.
>> Doesn't your portfolio deserve the best?
Then join Tasty Trade, Investopedia's
best platform for options trading 2026.
Trade smarter with advanced charting
tools, back testing, a pre-built
strategy selector, and more features.
Join Tasty Trade today and earn a double
commission rebate up to $3,000 total on
your stock and ETF option trades for 30
days. Visit tastyrade.com/hat
for more info. All applicable
regulatory, exchange, and clearing fees
still apply. Options involve risks and
are not suitable for all investors.
Learn more about Tasty Trade promo terms
and conditions at tastyrade.com/double.
Offer expires May 31st, 2026. Tasty
Trade Incorporated as a registered
broker dealer and member of FINRA NFA
and SIPC changed everything. I mean, was
that you think one of the most
significant aha moments in your trading?
Just realizing I no longer have to chase
breakouts. I can just click the sell
button and short these things. And from
there, that's the opportunity that you
seek. I was like, "Dude, if this thing
is going to go down anyway, why don't I
just hit the other button and see what
happens?" Right? Every time I buy, the
same second, dude, the same second it
crashes, right? Because I was buying in
all the wrong spots. You know, most of
the time, you know, when you're buying
the breakout in the wrong type of
market, that's liquidity for sellers,
right? And I didn't know that. And I
actually remember because it was funny
at the time, you know, I was still
obviously living with my parents,
brother, this that and you know, I
remember and I had that thousand trade
and I remember leaving my bedroom and
walking to my brother's room who was
about two years younger than me and he
was like selling he was like flipping
sneakers, right? So he was like flipping
sneakers and you know he was maybe
making I don't know 50 bucks a sneaker.
I don't whatever it was back then. And I
was like, Allan, like I just made
$1,000. He's like, "What?" I was like,
"Dude, I just made $1,000." And he just
like couldn't compute it. Like cuz like,
dude, I'm Starbucks. He's selling
sneakers. Like the most money, you know,
it would take us months to make $1,000,
you know, and I made it in a day. So, I
would say that was definitely one of the
more significant trades that I did
simply because it gave me hope. It gave
me hope that wait a second, did I just
discover something that is going to
change my life? You know, back then my
goal was very simple. I want to make 100
grand a year. I thought that 100 grand a
year was rich. These days, 100 grand a
year, you're still poor. It's crazy.
But, you know, that's kind of that's
kind of what I was shooting for and
aiming for. And, you know, eventually
turned to $100,000 days. It turned into
wow,
>> you know, $100,000 losses as well. But
the reality is that that moment of VGGL,
it's crazy because the stock is
delisted,
>> you know? I can't even like
>> Yeah,
>> I can't I I tried to
>> can't reminisce. Can't go look at it.
Where did I get in? Where did I get out?
Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean, look, I tried to uh frame
it one day like uh that that day
>> in sometime in 2014, whatever.
>> That's the most important trade for you.
I mean, it really is.
>> Yeah. forget the hund like the $100,000
trades wouldn't have happened without
that, right? So, that trade was so
important because that it gave you that
hope. Now, you mentioned VGGL is
delisted. Now, I I'm curious, have you
thought about over the last
12 years of your trading journey.
Looking back, how many of the tickers
and small cap land that you've shorted
that are delisted?
>> A lot. A lot. I would say probably I
mean you know I've been trading 12 years
now. I've traded thousands tens of
thousands of stocks feels like probably
I would say a conservative estimate is
like 20% of them are gone like gone gone
gone. It might be more but just a rough
math in my head is like at least 20% of
the stocks that I trade are disappeared
forever
you know
>> just delisted gone. So do you think that
I mean you paid that early tuition early
in your journey. Do you think most
traders need that early on they they
they learn in those draw downs they have
to experience the losses or can they
just
uh can they just learn without crashing
the plane as edu trades would say. I I
love that analogy. He said I don't have
to crash the plane to learn how to be a
pilot. Do you have to crash the plane?
Do you need those losses? What do you
think?
>> 100%. I've not met a single successful
trader that has not
struggled at the start. You know, the
best example is I actually recently did
a podcast with Lance Brightstein who's
made $100 million. He's in the Market
Wizards book and he said he was the
worst trader in the world. So much so
that he was about to look for another
job. His his his firm was sick and tired
of his losses and he was unable to
really find any type of success for a
couple years. That guy went on to be a
market wizard making $100 million. So, I
think that all of the greatest traders
have to go through some sort of struggle
because that struggle will teach you
risk management. That struggle will
teach you how to be humble. That
struggle will teach you how to grade
your setups. Without struggle, without
failure, you will not know what you're
capable of, and you will not know what
works. You know, if you just started
trading and you had a little bit of
beginner's luck, eventually that
beginner's luck is going to run out.
Whether it be market cycles, whether it
be change in conditions, but the
fundamentals of risk management, the
fundamentals of grading your setups, the
fundamentals of fundamental analysis,
you know, will give you that foundation.
And what you have to understand about
trading is the same thing as a house.
The foundation is the the most important
part. Without a strong foundation, you
cannot build a skyscraper. You know, as
soon as you start building on a shittyh
foundation, Yeah. your building's going
to collapse. You know,
>> you said over the years, too, you've
developed more of a healthy risk uh just
a healthy, I guess, approach towards
your trading and towards risk, unless
you you just respect it more. what what
happened along the way where you said
you know I I got to start having more of
a healthy respectful attitude towards uh
towards this risk.
>> Yeah. I mean I think that as a trader
the question becomes how much pain do
you want to take before you learn your
lesson? You know, and me being a
stubborn
kid, it took me a while to learn these
lessons. And it's like, how many times
do you want to lose more than your risk?
How many times do you want to get
yourself out of a hole? How many times
do you want to struggle and suffer and,
you know, be upset with yourself until
you finally, you know, learn your
lesson? And for me, I realized that I
was a deer in headlights. So anytime a
stock would go against me or anytime I
would get into trouble, man, I just
couldn't click the button. I just
couldn't click it. You know what I'm
saying? So I had to have the broker come
in and do it for me. What does that
mean? I had to set a max loss auto
liquidation. So if my account got to
minus $5,000,
I wouldn't even have to click the mouse.
I would get auto liquidated out.
>> Okay? you know, if I would add to my
losers consistently, I would set a max
size on my account. So, let's say it's
10,000 shares. I could not keep adding
to a loser and add to a loser over
10,000 shares and balloon my risk. So,
adding these guard rails that the
broker, the technology helped me was
able to kind of scale my trading. So
something to keep in mind is when we are
trading you have to understand that
there are there's retail traders like
us. Then there's the professional Wall
Street traders. A professional Wall
Street trader has someone called a risk
manager. A risk manager's full-time job
is to monitor your trades and if you're
getting a little bit sloppy, tap you on
the shoulders. What's your plan? What
are you doing here? As retail traders,
we don't have that. So, we need to have
our retail brokers act as our risk
managers to protect ourselves from
ourselves. You know, what would your
trading look like if capital wasn't the
constraint? That's the reality for most
traders. It's not skill holding them
back. It's size. Trade the pool changes
that. Step into the US equity markets
with up to $200,000 in buying power
without committing your own capital.
Full access to stocks and ETFs, long or
short, executed with the precision and
freedom. Serious traders expect your
performance is measured by one standard.
Disciplined risk management and
consistent execution. Meet that standard
and you operate at scale. No
subscriptions, no ongoing obligations,
just a clear path forward. For those
ready to trade beyond limitations, this
is the next level.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah. The just the max loss on the
account the broker liquidates to you. Do
you man that you know that resonates for
me too? It's something I apply. Do you
think most traders need something like
that? because we often times get in our
own way, right? I mean, that's what you
hear on the trading journey. It's not
necessarily the edge is not necessarily
the strategy. The edge is the
discipline, right? To like stick to it
and often times we don't stick to it.
You think that's a rule that most should
apply?
>> I think every trader should do it. I
think 100% of traders should do it. Um
because the reality is that in the
trading game, in the trading business,
you know, at the end of the day, you
know, any idiot can make money in the
market, but the people that last long
time are the ones that keep that money.
And I feel like a lot of traders, you
know, they the main thing that always
happens is like, you know, they get into
a hot streak and they're making a little
bit of money and as soon as the hot
streak stops and they're faced with
adversity with any type of stock, they
keep keep consistently adding to a loser
and adding to a loser and adding to a
loser so that they don't stop their hot
streak. And let's say their hot streak
yielded to $10,000 in profits. They end
up blowing up 50k. they end up blowing
up way more than what their streak was.
So, a very basic rule that I give for
setting risk parameters is this. Your
max loss auto liquidation should be no
more than two days worth of your
trading. What does that mean? If you
make $100 a day trading, your max loss
auto liquidation should be $200. That
way, on your worst possible day, it
takes 2 days to make it back. What
people do is they make $100 a day and
they set their max loss to 5K. takes
them freaking so long to make it back.
It makes no sense. So that's what I
would first start off by doing is set
your max loss all liquidation and no
more than two days worth of your work.
Because the reality is how many times as
traders, myself included, we said, "All
right, um you know, my max risk is 500
bucks. If it goes to 500 bucks, I'm
going to stop out." Goes to 500, you
don't stop out. Then it goes to 700 and
you're like, "If it goes just back to
500, I'll get out." Then it goes to
a,000 and you're like, "Please go to
700, I'll get out. ETH loss and it goes
to 2, three, 4,000, you blow up your
entire month and you're like, "What the
hell did I just do?" But if you just had
that broker kick in at $500, you would
have been so much calmer. You would have
been so much more chill and you would
have probably made back that loss the
next day. So, I think it's it's
mandatory as a retail trader to have
some sort of loss limits in place
because that's like jumping out of a
plane and not having a parachute. That's
like driving a Ferrari and not having a
seat belt, you know? was like hopping in
the water with sharks and not having a
shark cage, right? I mean, you could do
it. You're probably going to [__]
die. [laughter]
>> I love those analogies. Uh longevity is
what you're speaking on. I mean, and
you've lasted here for a long time and
over the years, I'm sure you've seen
many, many traders fall by the wayside
and even probably consistent traders,
which is why I want to touch on this
risk management portion. H how many
traders have you seen that are they're
really good traders, but they apply then
too much risk on that one trade or on
one day or one week or one month even.
They're not zoomed out enough to the
point where it just breaks your heart.
You say, "Man, this is a great trader,
but his ego took over. He went way too
heavy on this trade." And then from
there, I'd also want to transition to
like where you you have a an account
size that I've heard you say you just
keep right around 50k maybe for that
risk management so you don't oversize
over leverage on setups. What are your
thoughts on on that?
>> Correct. So two things. Let's start with
number one. So number one is how many
traders have I seen that just have the
talent but don't have the risk
management? And I knew a guy and this
guy would make
consistently like over 20 days he'd be
green every day and over those 20 days
he'd make 100k and then that one red day
comes 120k minus and just that same
cycle over and over and over and over
and over again. Needless to say that
person's not around anymore. He had the
talent for making 100k in 20 days but
every time he had one possible red day
gone. And also something to keep in mind
is there's those people that, you know,
risk too much. Then there's the people
that are the complete opposite of the
spectrum that are scared to lose 20
bucks. I had a friend that, you know,
sports bets like 300 bucks a day. But
when he gets into trading, you know,
he's betting 20 bucks on a loss and he's
freaking out. Like what the hell are you
doing? You're gambling more on freaking
sports betting, but you know, a tenth of
it on trading, you're freaking out. So
there has to be kind of like a middle
ground of,
you know, you have to be not only
accepting of risk, but you can't be
scared of it either. You know, some
people are just deathly afraid of losing
20 bucks. And if that's the case, you
know, maybe trading is not for you. So
I've seen both ends of the spectrum. You
know, well, you started out with the
$2,000 account, right? And then you
you've grown it and grown it and grown
it. I mean, how how do can you talk to
the person out there who's listening who
is scared of that risk? Like they they
have a smaller account and they don't
know how to size up to that next level
where you you kind of were able to
embrace that risk. How how can that
trader embrace that risk?
>> Yeah. So, I think it's really important
is number one is if you do not know the
grade of your setup, you have not earned
the ability to size up yet. And it's
very very simple to understand because
the reality is whenever someone wants to
get into trading they want to start
sizing up immediately right it's like
you know uh you know you start trading
you see all these you know Instagram
videos these YouTube videos the cars the
watches this that and then you know
you're trying to replicate that with a
$1,000 account it's going to be very
very difficult and what you have to
remember is maybe it might be a good
idea to kind of you know share a little
bit about me is my first year trading I
lost money. My second year I broke even
when I discovered short selling. My
third year I started to make like a
hundred bucks a day, right? So by my
like fourth year is when I started to
really excel in trading. So what I think
people have to understand is even making
a very small $50 to $100 a day is not
the point of that is not to change your
life. The point of that is to prove that
you understand the market and understand
you know very simple market conditions
because at the end of the day you could
always add a zero at the end of your
share size right but to kind of
backtrack is I need I think people need
to realize that size is reserved for the
best setups only right it's like what is
like the perfect opportunity right
perfect opportunities don't happen you
know every single day every single week
perfect opportunities happen once or
twice a year. You know, some of the most
recent examples I can think of is during
April of last year when President Trump
announced a 90-day pause market ripped
up. That's a once in a decade
opportunity, you know, or, you know,
even more recently Beyond Meat when it
went from like 50 cents to like $8 back
down to like three bucks, you know, that
was a once a year type of opportunity,
you know. So there's always going to be
these or even you know the GameStop the
AMC's and all these other crazy runners
you know once in a couple year
opportunities. So you have to tell
yourself is the opportunity that I'm
trading similar to that? And if the
answer is yes that's when you get
aggressive. If the answer is no you just
sit around and scalp around. So for me
every day that I show up I'm not looking
to make $100,000 although I would like
to. You know if the opportunity is not
there then I'm not going to be
aggressive. So, I always just try to
show up and just ask like, is this a day
to size up based on a high
[clears throat] probability setup or is
this a day I'm sizing up just because I
feel like it? And if it's just because I
feel like it, God bless, I'm probably
dead for the day, you know?
>> Right. So, what do you think about that
saying then that 90% of your profits are
made on 10% of the trades? Do you think
that's true?
>> It's accurate for me.
>> Okay. for most traders I know you know
like the biggest trades I had you know
uh you know the multi6 figure days those
are the days that you know end up
creating my big P&Ls but every day that
I'm showing up to the market I'm making
five or 10 grand scalping you know I'm
adding some extra P&L to my bottom line
I'm staying in tune with the market
because the reality is that you know if
you just show up for those big days call
it four times a year once a quarter to
make the math easy if you show up for
those big days and you screw it up, oh
man, you're dead. You're dead. So, by
being in tune with the market and by
trading every single day, I am seeing
all right, what is the sentiment of the
market? What is working? What is not
working? Because if I'm blindly not
looking at the market, I won't know that
maybe uh the stocks that are fading in
this quarter are stocks that are pushing
for two days and then on the third day
they're failing. If that's what I've
been seeing and monitoring in the
market, well, if I just don't do that
and I come back and I see, oh, the stock
is running on day two, I might be dead.
So, the day-to-day trades are to kind of
keep you in tune with the market in my
opinion as you wait for those big Super
Bowl style opportunities that come once
a quarter, you know, and in just
recently in this last quarter, we had
gold, silver, and oil, you know.
>> I love that. Yeah. I mean, that's that's
excellent. Um, so [sighs and gasps]
do you still keep your kind of your back
against the wall, if you will, with the
35 or 50,000 that you have in the
account? Where where are you with that
now? And do you and when those
opportunities present themselves, that
once a quarter opportunity, do you,
let's say, even wire in money at that
point and say, "Hey, I'm hammering this.
Let's let's put the risk on at this
point."
>> Yeah, great question. So when I first
started trading, you know, I would use,
you know, more of like because you have
to have like because PDT is going to go
away sometime this year, but you know,
the PDT rule is 25K and you need to have
at least like 30K in your account for
like a little bit of a buffer. So when I
finally got over that hump and had
enough to, you know, fund my account
with that, you know, I would keep my
account around 35K, which gave me like a
10K buffer. And every time that my
account grew to $50,000, I would wire
out 15K. I put that in my bank account.
Put that in my bank account. Put that in
my bank account. You know, now, you
know, it's kind of similar to the thing.
You know, I've been kind of keeping it
around like 50K, 60K. Every time I get
to 100, I wire it out. But what I do is
on those very, very big opportunities, I
definitely wire in. Now, this is a more
advanced type of thing. I do not suggest
that most traders do this cuz most
traders do not know what the proper uh,
you know, high probability setups are.
But yeah, I have no problem, you know,
wiring into my account, taking advantage
of that opportunity, and then wiring
back out because the reality is that for
90% of the year, I don't really need a
big account. You know, I just need a big
account for those 10% of the setups. And
when those 10% of the setups come, I
have no problem, you know, wiring in
more aggressively into my account to
give me that buying power that I need to
capitalize. But for new traders, I mean,
that's very, very difficult to
understand. And I do not suggest that
unless you've been trading for a while
and know exactly exactly what your best
setups are cuz otherwise you're going to
you're going to balloon your losses in
my in my opinion.
>> This is what you're known for and why
you're a legend. You you just you know
the A+ setup. You know how to really
just lean into it and take advantage of
it. Uh and I heard you even recently say
you think newer traders should I mean
they should get out of that habit of
adding to losers and in instead adding
to winners. Now, it's challenging
emotionally from what I heard because
what what happens is, you know, you add
to the winner. Well, now your average is
coming down. So, the tra traders have a
hard time getting comfortable with that.
H how can traders become comfortable
adding to their winners?
>> Yeah. So, this is I have a kind of a
controversial take on this and you know,
this is just kind of the way that I
think about it is uh you know, I say
screw your average, man. Screw your
average. Why?
If the stock is going in your favor, I
don't care what my average is because
the more the stock goes in my favor, the
higher my win rate gets on the stock.
Let me give you an example.
>> So, let's say I'm going short a stock,
meaning I want the stock to go down and
I'll make money. Well, if a stock has a
death candle, that signals a change in
trend. Maybe my win rate on the setup
goes from 50% to 65%. And let's say
after that it breaks VWAP, right? Then
my win rate goes from 65% to 75%. And
then after it breaks VWAP, it breaks the
low of the day. Then my win rate goes
from 75% to probably 85 or 90%. So at
that point when we have a death candle,
a break of VWAP, and a break of low of
the day, the the win rate gets so
aggressively higher for the stock to go
down that I should just be focused on
adding to my winner because the win rate
is going to be so dramatically higher
versus then adding to a loser.
Everyone's always afraid about having
this perfect average, the perfect
average, the perfect average. Perfect
average doesn't matter if the stock is
going against you, right? But if the
stock is going in your favor and you are
being proven right, it is your job as a
trader to get more aggressive when you
are proven right versus more aggressive
when you're proven wrong. Here's an
analogy. Your house is on fire. Do you
think the best way to get your house out
of fire is to add more fire, add more
gas? or do you think you should add
water? When a house is on fire, that
means your trading is wrong. That means
you're wrong on a trade. These idiots
are adding gasoline to their fire.
They're making their fire larger and
larger and they're like, "Why the hell
is my house burning down faster?" It's
like, [laughter] "What the hell?" You
know, but that again, that takes me a
while to understand, but that's the way
that you have to think about it is when
you're in a losing trade, your house is
on fire. When you're adding to your
loser, when the house is on fire, you're
adding gas. the house is going to burn
down faster. What you should do is get
the hell out of that house as fast as
possible and won't look back.
>> You know,
>> that is so good. Screw the average. F.
What you're essentially saying is focus
on making money instead of trying to be
right, you know, with the perfect uh
average on the ticker that the stock is
going in your favor. If your plan is
getting proved correct, what people end
up doing is when they are proven correct
and it's going in their favor, they take
the profit. When they are wrong and it's
going against them, they get in larger.
It should be the inverse. As a stock is
going against you, get out. As the stock
is going for you, get bigger. You know,
it's like it's it's like ex it's like
you must bet bigger when you are proven
correct. So again, let's say that same
example. The stock reclaimed the VWAP.
It reclaimed low of the day. It went
back to the high of the day. Whatever it
did, I mean, trading is not perfect.
You're not going to win every single
time. You're not going to win on every
single trade, but at least you gave
yourself the best possible opportunity
to get in larger on the setup. You know,
I'm trying to think of one of the most
recent examples that we've seen. I mean,
you know, silver, oil, and gold have
been kind of crazy, right? It's like if
you remember uh when oil I think it was
about 2 or 3 weeks ago when oil had that
big big big gap up and it started to
sell off. I think it gapped up to
likeund something a barrel and just
started to slowly sell off slowly sell
off slowly sell off right and then Trump
came out with news that you know the war
was over. It was BS but the war was
over. Oil collapsed 10% more.
>> So when you're being proven right think
about this. When you're shorting oil
like that and your thesis is oil is
going to fade, it's going to come down
and the news of Trump comes out that you
know the war is over and oil collapses.
Does it make more sense to exit your
position there or to get an even more
aggressive because now you have a
catalyst to back you up? What most
traders do is when they see that backup,
when they see that they are being proven
correct, they're like, "Oh, cool. You
know, I made a little bit of money." But
no, when you're proven correct, get in
bigger, you know, especially if the
setup warrants it. And that's the thing
that I think is super super super slept
on is people love adding to their
losers. They love scalping out of their
winners and they wonder why the hell am
I not making money because I every time
my house is burning down, I'm adding gas
to it. I mean, it's logical if you think
about it. And I always like to teach
with analogies because analogies help
him be real, you know. Are you ready to
get serious about options trading? Then
join Tasty Trade, Investopedia's best
platform for options trading 2026.
Stocks, options, futures, and more.
Tasty Trade has everything you trade all
in one platform. Get low commissions,
including a $10 cap per leg on options
trades, so you can keep more of what you
earn. Tasty Trade is packed with
advanced charting tools, back testing, a
pre-built strategy selector, and more
features to help you trade smarter.
Manage your positions with speed and
precision using active [clears throat]
trader mode, one-click trading, and
smart order tracking. Plus, Tasty Trade
Stellar Trade Desk team offers live
support during trading hours if you need
it. Join Tasty Trade today and earn a
double commission rebate up to $3,000
total on your stock and ETF option
trades for 30 days. Visit
tastyrade.com/hat
for more info. All applicable regulatory
exchange and clearing fees still apply.
Options involves risk and are not
suitable for all investors. Learn more
about Tasty Trade promo terms and
conditions at tastyrade.com/double.
Offer expires May 31st, 2026. Tasty
trade incorporated is a registered
broker, dealer, and member of FINRA NFA
and SIPC. So, I have a question
regarding that. I got a lot. Uh, but
this one specifically because I've seen
some respectable traders, you know, they
they they they size into their positions
without ne they break up their full
position, let's say. So, is that adding
or scaling? For example, if I plan, you
know, a thousand shares short on this
ticker, maybe I start with 200 and size
into it. Is there an appropriate way to
put fuel on on your house or is it all
fuel and it's just you should
>> No, no, Greg. That's I think that's a
fantastic question and it's going to be
good that we clear this up. So, okay.
So, I'm going to be talking just on the
short bias side of the market because
that's kind of where my niche is, right?
So, everything that I say, if you're
long, do the damn opposite. So, okay.
So, let's say I'm looking to short a
stock, right? I have a rule and my rule
is if a stock is above VWAP, the volume
weighted average price, I am not allowed
to use more than 30% of my max size.
Why? is because I don't want to add to a
loser, right? So, let's say my max size
on the setup, again, for math, is 1,000
shares, right? So, I want to go max size
on a setup that has it's going to be
1,000 shares.
If the stock is above VWAP going against
me, 30% is the max size that I'm going
to use. So, that' be 300 shares. So, if
it's above VWAP, I will not be allowed
to use more than 300 shares. Now, as
each time I get a confirmation signal,
right, a signal that I am being proven
right, I'll add to my winner. What does
that mean? If the stock then breaks
VWAP, I will get to 50% of my size. If
the stock then breaks low of the day,
I'll get to 75% of my size. And then
what I like to do is I always like to
take a little bit of profit off the
table because whenever I take a little
bit of profit off the table, it helps me
be patient and in case the stock
bounces, I could repurpose some of those
profits as a re-short. So for me, every
time I get a signal proving me right,
that's when I add. So if you're a long
buys trader, if it reclaims VWAP, you
add to your winner. If it reclaims the
high of the day, you add to your winner.
If it reclaims the pre-market high of
the day, you add to your winner. So,
every time that you're getting proven
right on any type of setup, any type of
signal, any type of something that says,
you know what, Kevin, my thought process
was I'm looking to short this stock and
it just did everything that I want. It
did everything I want and that's when
I'm going to get aggressive. So, I think
that's super super key. And I think
that's super super valuable for most
people as well as understand you're not
just sizing up just because you feel
like it. I mean, if I size up just
because I felt like it, man, I mean, I
don't know. I mean, I feel like it every
day, man, I'm feeling hot, you know?
Right. [laughter]
>> The reality is that you know at the end
of the day you know I just want to make
sure that you know whenever there is a
signal whenever there's a reason
whenever there is a proven fact in the
chart emphasizing my idea. Go for it
baby. Go for it. Go for it. Okay. Let's
say that that trade the where you're
taking 30% uh max of the share size.
Let's say it go it goes it goes against
you, you know, it in invalidates. Are
you taking one just hard stop on one one
exit or are you breaking that exit up
into multiple positions? How do you go
about that?
>> Well, for me, what I've realized is
this. It is a lot easier to stop out of
your position when you have 30% of your
size on than it is 50% or,000%. So back
in the day before I had this rule in
place, I would stop out of half and then
if it keeps going against me, I stop out
of the other half. But now with 30% of
my size, man, I could close my eyes and
stop out. It doesn't it's it's like a
paper cut rather than a dagger, you
know? Love it. Great analogy. So, do you
think for I know we're talking sizing
and you talked about grading your
setups, which I think is huge, but for
the newer trader, I mean it
[clears throat] they have to essentially
throw darts, you know, before they
figure out like what where's my edge,
where does it lie, what's my setup,
which we're going to dive into yours.
So, do you think for the newer trader
that they should be sizing in and out of
trades or do you think they should keep
their sizing fairly consistent until
they do know how to grade like you're
saying?
>> I think in this day and age, there's so
many different tools out there, whether
it be, you know, these trading journals
that are, you know, 20 bucks a month,
but even if you don't have 20 bucks a
month, man, AI is incredible. What you
should do is you should take your
trades, upload them into AI, and just
tag them like, "Hey, this is a trade
that I didn't do right on. This I did
right on. This, you know, what I'm
making money on." I learned so obviously
AI didn't exist when, you know, I was
uh, you know, around. But what I would
do is I would upload my trades into
Trading View, Trader View, whatever it
is. And I learned so many so many things
about myself. Here's what I learned. I
learned that I make the most amount of
money on stocks $2 to $10. I learned
that I make uh the most amount of my
money from $930 to 1030. So, if I learn
that I make most amount of my money from
$2 and $10, I don't trade under $2. I
don't really trade over $10 unless it's
a very big opportunity. If I learn that
I make most of my money between 9:30 and
10:30, I don't trade before 9:30. I
don't trade after 10:30. Uh, I learned
that I lose the most amount of money on
Mondays. Why do I lose the most amount
of money on Mondays? I'm so excited over
the weekend to trade that I get
overeager on Mondays. So, I try to size
down on Mondays. You know, I learned
that I have a 75% win rate. So, anytime
my win rate is under 75%, that maybe I
should start slowing down. What the
hell's going on, Alex? Something's
changing. You know, I learned that if I
don't get enough sleep during the night,
I don't perform well. I learned that if
I'm hung over when I'm trading, I don't
trade well. I learned that if I fight
with my girl or fight with my friends, I
don't trade well. So, all these little
things that, you know, may seem little
in the moment told me exactly what I
need to know. I don't trade before 9:30,
I don't trade after 10:30 anymore. You
know, I don't trade as aggressively on
Mondays. You know, I walk away. If I
have a fight with my girl, if I don't
get enough sleep, I'm sizing down. So,
that took me years and years and years
of my data to track. And the reality is
that you know the only way you could
find what works for you is you have to
track your own stats because every
single person is a different type of
trader man. We are all different
traders. We have all different things
that we work on. We have all different
things that we struggle with. And the
reality is my trading mistakes are not
going to be your trading mistakes. You
know maybe for me the fact that you know
uh you know I actually know it's going
to sound crazy. I know a trader that
trades way better when he's drunk. Why?
He's He's
trading through instinct. He's tra he's
been a 20-year-old trader. He's
>> Do you trade with him every day?
>> Uh is B, you know, is B. I'll throw I'll
throw him under the bus a little bit
just for education, but you know, I
can't tell him that. But he's a way
better trader when he's drunk because
he's he's not thinking. He's just
reacting. It's like I'll give you an
example. The first time you started
learning how to drive a car, you know,
you'd be like, "Am I in the lanes? Did I
pull my signal up? Did I turn left and
right four seconds at the stop sign?"
Now, when you get in the car, you don't
even think. You just do. You just do.
So, that's the way it is in trading is
after you get good enough, you stop
thinking about it. It's intuition,
right? It becomes intuition which I was
going to ask you too.
>> Do you still have to really track and
journal these days like you did back
then or it's just intuition like you
know you just know you just know when to
size up size down not to trade on you
know size down on Mondays all of that.
>> [snorts]
>> The honest truth is I should be tracking
my stats more, you know, but after 12
years and $16 million, I've gotten a
little bit lazy, but I definitely
because now I know. Now I know. I mean,
it's not really going to change from
here, you know. Maybe the little nuances
might change a little bit, you know, but
the reality is that I know everything
about my personal trading. I know where
I'm an idiot. I know where I excel. And
yeah, so that's kind of I think all new
traders, no matter what, no matter what,
have to track because you don't know.
You don't know what is working for you.
I could say that, you know what, my best
setups are the first red day. Turns out
maybe you suck at first red days, but
you're better at buying a VWAP reclaim,
whatever it is. If you don't know that,
then you're going to be sizing up on all
the wrong setups, you know.
>> Yeah. Let's talk about that core edge. I
mean that you've traded consistently
over the years that that first red day.
I mean what has why has that worked so
well consistently over the years that
first red day that you continue to
trade?
>> As long as human greed and human fear
and human emotions don't change, the
patterns will not change. What does that
mean? The reason why a first red day
works so well is because it capitalizes
on the human greed. stock goes from $2
to $5, then $5 to $10, and $10 to $20,
and $20 to $4, $4 to $60. Like, baby,
it's going to 100, right? And then all
of a sudden, the first day that it
doesn't continue to extend is the day
that it tops out because all of these
inexperienced longs keep averaging down
to their loser, whereas the smart money
is selling into their liquidity. You
know, ever watch a stock rip and think,
"I could have nailed that if I had real
capital." The truth is, many capable
traders never reach their potential. Not
due to lack of skill, but lack of scale.
Trade the Pool was built to solve
exactly that. A firm designed for
serious individuals who want access to
the US equity markets with meaningful
buying power up to $200,000 without
committing their own capital. Get access
to virtually every stock and ETF. Go
long or short freely with the
flexibility professional traders expect.
You're evaluated on one thing, your
ability to manage risk and execute with
consistency. Meet the standard and you
trade at scale. No subscriptions, no
ongoing commitments. Whether you're
still refining your strategy, a trader
with experience who hasn't yet broken
through, or a seasoned professional
simply looking for more capital, Trade
the Pool is built to meet you where you
are and take you that next step further.
The markets have evolved. Access has
evolved. Now, so has the way traders
operate within them. Trade the pool.
>> Absolutely. Now, with some of these
plays, I've heard you say early on, you
may have those like the 50% runners.
Like, let's take the first example. You
said a stock that goes from two to five.
And that would be a significant move
what 10 years ago. But then it kind of
transitioned into you getting 200, 300,
400, 500. that greed you're talking
about just taken over
uh over the years. And so, how do you
identify, okay, this is this is the
first red day and they're not just kind
of trapping you and sending it up to the
next thousand%.
>> Yeah. I mean, look, the the reason why
the first red day works is it's the
first day that it goes red. You cannot
anticipate the move. You have to wait
for it to go red and then attack it, you
know? So that that's kind of what helps
build, you know, this patience aspect
is, for example, one of the biggest
first red days for me this year was on
gold. I made around $200,000 on gold and
I think I have the live trading video on
YouTube. So every day I trade live and
then I post those replays on YouTube.
But uh the reason why gold worked out is
cuz it was a multi-day runner that
pushed and pushed and pushed and then
finally gapped up towards 5500ish or GLD
was around 505 and then when it gapped
up and finally sold off, I mean that was
the top forever. And I'm uh referencing
the first red day on uh January 29,
2026. That's the top for a very very
long time. It had on January 27, January
28, gapped up, gapped up, third day gap
up, went red, and it was gone forever,
you know. True. And it just to me the
trade got initiated not on the gap up.
The gap up gave me
some
I would say the gap up gave me kind of
like it's like a shark that has blood in
the water, right? you you know the shark
is starting to look around you know he
smells a little bit of blood you know he
sees what's about to happen and then
when it goes red is attack you know love
it so you've been around so many you
know highlevel traders including the
time you had at SMB Capital from the
best traders that you've seen what what
do you really think separates them you
from everybody else
>> brother I love this question and I just
want to give you some prophecies there's
some amazing questions so
Man, I've been fortunate enough to know
seven, eight, and nine figure traders.
And I think the one thing that they have
in common is the love of the game,
meaning trading is their passion. It's
something that they want to keep
learning about. It's something that, you
know, gets them excited. and also
willingness to keep learning. So, I
found that the traders that make the
most amount of money don't just say,
"Hey, I'm Alex. I made $16 million. I
don't need to learn anything anymore. I
don't need to do anything." Cuz what I
understand is that every time I place a
trade,
there's someone else on the other side
of the trade. Every time you place a
trade, you're trading against me, right?
So, what has been really, really
important to me is I've always been
willing to learn from other people. You
know, someone like Lance that's made,
you know, five times more money than me,
I'm watching his YouTube videos every
single day. You know, I'm reaching out
to him via text. I'm asking him
questions. You know, I'm I'm trying to
learn from someone like him or another
guy, Phil, who's in the Market Wizards
book. I talk to him very often. you
know, Jack Kellogg and all these other
people as well is I'm always willing to
learn from traders that have, you know,
made more than me. Um, because the
reality is I have still so much to
learn. And I often feel like, you know,
maybe inexperienced traders or traders
that have too much of an ego do not last
because they think they know it all. And
the reality is the moment that you think
you know it all, you actually know
nothing. So I think the most elite
traders are not only obsessed with the
game but also willing to learn and also
willing to drop their ego aside, remain
humble and
you know just continue to improve
dayto-day. You know it's very funny
because even to this day no matter how
much money I've made I am still watching
trading videos. I am still watching
trading podcast. I am still watching
anything that has to do with trading
because I'm looking for that next edge
that I could learn from someone else.
>> Oh, that's so amazing. You know, that's
it really is a consistent theme I've
heard since doing these interviews is
passion. And that was my f next question
was that I've watched so many of your
interviews and what I have seen that
stands out to me is the passion. A lot a
lot of traders approach this like you
said thinking that there's some kind of
a finish line where they no longer have
to learn. essentially they get
complacent like they get comfortable
>> but then conversation I had with Edu
said he said as soon as you start
getting comfortable you know that's when
you're not going to grow you you have to
always kind of be uncomfortable because
that's where you learn to grow. Uh so I
thought that that was really fascinating
and you can tell the passion that you
have and just constantly wanting to
improve yourself. That's what it sounds
like. It's it just elevates you to the
next level and it's a it's a common
theme. It's like the bloodstream
essentially uh of your trading journey
is just having that passion to take it
to the next level. So that's excellent.
Thank you so much for for sharing that.
>> 100%. And that's that's the reality is
like the moment that you think you know
it all, you're an idiot. Seriously, you
know, it's like think about how much I'm
still learning. Think about how much
I've made and how much I'm still
learning. And you know, it's funny
because like I said, people are trading
on the other side of the screen of me.
So you got to think, I mean, I want
those people to be as uneducated as
possible, as stupid as possible, as dumb
as possible because at the end of the
day, you know, the less work that they
put in, the better, you know?
>> Yeah. Do do you think that traders end
up they focus too much on making money
rather than the money part being a
byproduct of just really good trading?
and they don't focus enough on, you
know, compounding the money because I've
heard that you've kind of transitioned
now into generating tra taking the
trading profits and allocating them more
into long-term investments to compound
wealth. So, is that something you're
still focused on right now?
>> Yeah, definitely. I mean, any extra
capital that I make, I try to invest it
elsewhere because the reality is like I
say trading will make you rich, but
investing will make you wealthy. So, my
goal is to generate income through
trading and take that income that I
generate through trading and then invest
it into longerterm assets. And, you
know, it's actually funny because
yesterday the market was down a ton and
I ended up buying a ton of stocks
yesterday for long-term investments and
today the market rebounded, you know,
almost like 2%. You know, incredible.
>> [snorts]
>> So, for uh Alex, for anyone that's
listening right now, earlier in their
journey, maybe struggling, questioning
if they can really make it, maybe
they're about to sell the rims off their
car, [laughter] what what would you tell
them that uh you're really mad that that
would make a difference for them? What
What piece of advice do you have for
them?
>> Yeah, I mean, the question is, how bad
do you want, right? If you if you say
you want it, but you're not willing to
put in the work, I mean, it's not worth
it. Just it's not. just buy a S&P 500
index and call it a day. But the reality
is that, you know, you have to you have
to love the game. You have to be
obsessed with it. And I don't know why
anyone wouldn't be obsessed with
changing their life. I don't know why
freedom. I don't know why anyone
wouldn't be obsessed that you could make
more money than a doctor, lawyer,
engineer combined in one day and change
your family's life. That to me is a very
easy obsession. You know, it's really
hard for me to give up chocolate cake
and ice cream. You know, there's it's
it's like for you know what you have to
do. You know that the way to lose weight
is diet and exercise, but everyone's
always looking for this magical ompic,
right? It's just at the end of the day
like trading is hard work. Trading is
difficult, but it's going to be the best
hard work and difficulty of your entire
life because the reality is it will
change your life if you do it right.
I've made more money in my 12 years of
trading than I ever thought I would make
in a lifetime trading. You know, and the
best part is, you know, I'm just getting
started. You know, what I have over
everyone else is I have time. I have,
you know, youth. I have, you know, my
age. I'm only 31. You know, maybe we'll
do this on another 10 year anniversary.
I'll be
>> 41.
41. Yeah. I like the Ompic analogy. It
sounds like a book. like the ozenic of
stock trading. [laughter] Let's could
run with it. What So what does winning
look like for you now? You're 31. You've
been doing it for 10 years. I mean, what
what are your goals that you're I see
you across social media. You're you're
so passionate still, so active. I mean,
what what are your goals?
>> Yeah, I mean, great question. So, man,
it's like, you know, just the transition
of goals between starting my career and
kind of where I'm at now is just so
different, man. It's so different. Like,
back then, like I said, my goal was to
make like 100 grand in a year, right? Uh
I always had this like kind of, you
know, this dream, right? I always I
don't know if you know Jay Leno, but Jay
Leno has like a he has an airplane
hanger filled with cars, and cars are my
passion. Like cars are the only thing
that, you know, after I'm done trading
for the day, you know, going out on the
road, palm trees, nice sun, nice
weather, windows down, music blasting,
that's what relaxes me. So cars are
something that I've always been
passionate about. It's always been my
dream to have, you know, a car for every
single day of the week. You know, I'm
pretty much at half the week right now,
I got four different cars, but, you
know, I could get every single car for
the day of the week that I want. But
reality is now my my goals have shifted
from less of materialistic items because
I've fortunate been fortunate enough to
have all that. I have the watches, I
have the cars, you know, I have the
house, but now I've kind of shifted my
focus to less stress in my trading, you
know, because trading can be very
stressful if you let it be. And I've
also transitioned to kind of enjoying my
life a little bit more, too. Is, you
know, think about it. I was waking up at
4:00 a.m. every single day for like 6,
seven years non-stop. So, I've been
sleeping in a little bit. Instead of
waking up at 4, I wake up at 6:00 now.
Um, been trying to travel a little bit
more, see the world, you know, because
I'm fortunate enough to now have the
nicest hotel rooms. I get to fly first
class. And, you know, I might as well do
it while I'm young. But the reality is,
I just want to enjoy my life a little
bit more. Stop and smell the roses
because, you know, I was obsessed. And I
am still obsessed with the game. But I
never really took my head out for air.
And it wasn't until I got married that,
you know, my wife kind of helped me, you
know, enjoy my life a little bit more
because I just be working all day
non-stop because I'm always just trying
to get better, right? I'm always trying
to get better. What's the next
opportunity? What's the next edge? I'm
not a commodities trader, but I started
trading oil, gold, and silver this year
because that's where the opportunity
was, you know? You don't just magically
wake up and, you know, start trading
these things. You have to learn the
vehicles, you know, so stuff like that.
But just trying to live a more
stressfree life, trying to go out and
drive as much as I can. You know, one of
my favorite cars. Um, I work from home
and I don't really leave the house. I
put probably like 25,000 miles on that
car just like driving around and having
a blast, you know? So, I just want to be
able to kind of, you know, do more of my
passion, which is driving cars, travel,
you know, experience new things in life,
uh, be less stressed, and give back to
the community by posting videos online.
You know, I've been posting videos for
five, six years now on YouTube. So,
>> yeah. Where where can the traders find
you? I mean, you're you're active across
social media. Where can they find you?
>> Yeah. So, I post day uh weekly live
trading videos on YouTube, YouTube.com.
Uh, Alex Teis M I C A L E X T E M I Z M
I C is the YouTube channel. And every
week I'm posting live trading videos,
I'm posting vlogs, I'm posting, you
know, anything and everything. So yeah,
I mean, I think that uh just being able
to give traders the help and support
that I wish I had when I first started,
I think is super super valuable. I mean,
I'm trading anyway. Why don't I just
record it? Right.
>> Right. That's amazing. Inspiring. Thank
you so much. Um, Alex Tiz, I mean, this
has just been an incredible video. Some
huge takeaways. Very inspiring. Uh,
traders, I hope you guys learned a lot.
Uh, I did. And let let us know. Leave a
comment down in the comment section
below. Of course, hit the like and
subscribe button and find Alex. He's all
over social media and eager to help you
out, traders. So, Alex, I appreciate you
coming back on Chat with Traders. We'll
see you in another 10 year, maybe
sooner. Maybe sooner.
>> Let's do this. If you made it to the end
of the video, comment 10 years so we
know you made it this far.
>> Yes. Love it. 10 years.
>> Cool.
>> Thank you, Alex.
>> Thank you.
>> You've reached the end of this episode
of Chat with Traders, but rest assured,
there are more episodes [music] loaded
with real market insight and zero hype
on the way soon. So, to stay updated
with each [music] great new release,
subscribe to the podcast and iTunes. And
we'd love it if you'd leave a rating and
review. We'll catch you next [music]
time on Chat with Traders.
[music]